A Guide to the China Medical Board, Inc. records, RG 1 FA065
Rockefeller Archive Center
- China Medical Board, Inc. (Tr) (Box 31, Folder 218)
  Treasurer's Office, 1932-1933, 1941-1947; Treasurer's Report, 1933-1951 (Austin, 1929; Dashiell, 1932-1937; Debevoise, 1933; Frank, 1930; Greene, 1932; Robinson, 1940-1943)
- China Medical Board, Inc. - Vincent, George E., 1928-1930 (Box 31, Folder 218A)
- China - Chinese (L) (Box 31, Folder 219)
  China Medical Journal, 1931-1935 (Greene); China Relief Mission, 1948 (Calvin; Drummond; Director; Gilpatrick); China Society of America, Inc.; Chinese Aid Council, Inc., 1945-1947; Chinese Architecture, 1930 (Ingalls); Chinese Consul, 1931, 1938; Chinese Cultural Society, 1932-1933; Chinese Educational Mission, 1933; Chinese Government; 1943, 1947-1948 (Ministry of Finance, 1920, 1946); Chinese Language Instruction, 1917-1925 (Ma Kiam).
  Items of special note in this folder include a description of Limping Sickness, found under the mark-up Chinese Aid Council.
  See also Oversized Folder 69, Item 5
- Chinese (M) - Chou (Box 31, Folder 220)
  Chinese Medical Association, 1932-1934, 1937, 1945; Chinese Medical Journal, 1934-1947 (See also - Publications - C.M.J., 1940); Chinese National Anthem, 1929; Chinese News Service, 1945; Chinese Physiological Society, 1934-1935; Chinese Red Cross Society, 1924; Chinese Republic, President of, 1921; Chinese Social and Political Science Association, 1945-1946; Chinese Student and Alumni Service, 1952; Chinese Students in America (General, 1926-1932; Chen, Stephen H., 1931-1933; Duggan, Stephen P., 1933; Eng, Richard T., 1933-1934; Green, 1930; Gunn, Selskar M., 1933; Hodges, Paul C., 1934; Hwang, Florence, 1934; Macmillan, Eva B. A., 1925; University of Illinois, 193;1 Wong, 1935); Chinese Surgical Society, 1947; Ching, Chin-chow, 1945; Chiu, Dorothy (see Chao, Fu-chen); Chiu, Fu-his, 1948-1950; Chou, Ting-chung, 1949-1950
- Chow-Chr (Box 32, Folder 221)
  Chow, Hua-kang, 1940-1941, 1946-1950; Chow, Shou-kai, 1943-1944; Christian Medical Association of India, 1931, 1934; Christian Medical Council for Overseas Work, 1939, 1946-1951; Christ's Hospital, 1943
- Chu-Chun (Box 32, Folder 222)
  Chu, Chang-keng, 1929-1932; Chu, Chi-hsuin (Ulric), 1943-1948; Chu, Chih-pu, 1946; Chu, Hsien-I, 1929, 1936; Chu, Hung-ying, 1946; Chu, Ing-jang, 1934-1935; Chu, (Kuei-ching) Irving, 1937-1940, 1948-1949; Chu, Keats, 1940, 1945-1947; Chu, (Chia-li) Kelly, 1950, 1963-1964; Chu, Lee-chung, 1935; Chu, Liang-wei, 1939, 1950-1954; Chu, Mao-ken, 1927, 1931-1932; Chu, Tsung-yao, 1938; Chu, Wen-ssu, 1934-1935; Chu, Ying-chang, 1936-1938, 1944-1946, 1954-1956; Chuan, Fan, 1926; Chuan, S. James, 1938-1939, 1944-1947, 1962; Chung, Huei-pan (William), 1949; Chung Foo Union Bank, 1935-1946-1947; Chung Ho Hospital, 1946 (Lim; Tsur).
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of Kelly C. L. Chu.
- Cl-Co (Box 32, Folder 223)
  Clark, Grover, 1933; Clark, John G., 1921-1923; Clinical Records, 1925, 1933-1946 (Hoeppli; Tsur); Clonorchiasis, 1923-1924 (Arnold; Cort; Faust; Herbsman; Houghton; Strong); Co-tui, Frank, 1923, 1927-1928, 1934-1938.
  Items of special note in this folder include Sale of Clinical Records as Waste, attached to a letter from Wang to Loucks (January 23, 1945), found under the mark-up Clinical Records.
- Coal Consumption, 1922-1929, 1938, 1946-1948 (Box 32, Folder 224)
  Comptroller; Director; Goodrich; Greene; Hogg; Houghton; Loucks; Resident Director; Stone & Webster; Watson; Williams
  See also Oversized Folder 69, Item 6
- Coe-Com (Box 32, Folder 225)
  Coe, Frantzel (Mrs. Walter R. Lewin), 1922-1923; Cohn, Alfred E., 1952; College of Physicians and Surgeons, 1947; College of the City of New York, 1953; Columbia University - Monroe, Paul (see Trustees - Monroe;) Columbia University - Rhoades, 1924; Commission for International Educational Reconstruction, 1947-1949; Committee on Foreign Affairs - Porter (see Greene, 1927); Committee of Professors, 1931; Commutation, 1928-1940 (Beal; Comptroller).
  Comparative Data, 1929, 1933: Administration - Greene; Budget (Greene); College Finances (Brierly; Dashiell); Investments (China Foundation; Greene).
- Comptroller, 1918-1938 (Box 32, Folder 226)
- Comptroller, 1939-1941 (Box 32, Folder 227)
- Comptroller, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 228)
- Comptroller, 1946 January-July (Box 33, Folder 229)
- Comptroller, 1946 August-December (Box 33, Folder 230)
- Comptroller, 1947 January-June (Box 33, Folder 231)
- Comptroller, 1947 July-December (Box 33, Folder 232)
- Comptroller, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 233)
- Comptroller, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 234)
- Comptroller, 1950, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 235)
- Conferences (Box 34, Folder 236)
  Buildings, July 1919; Buildings and Equipment, February 1919; Chinese Exchange, 1920; Commutation, 1926; Far East Conference, 1922; Gedney Farms, February 1921, May 1921; Hot Springs, Virginia, 1920; Peking, 1921; Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) General, 1920; Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Organization, 1920; Purpose and Policy, 1919; Religious Qualifications, 1924
- Confidential Reports on Staff (A-M) (Box 34, Folder 237)
  General - Greene, 1929; Abbott, Lucy, 1923; Alloway, 1927; Anderson, B. G., 1929; Anderson, Dagny Viola Josephina, 1933; Arndt, Lydia, 1923; Banfield, Gertrude, 1924; Barchet, H., 1929; Barton, Maude, 1923; Bauer, J. H., 1926; Beaty, M. Louise, 1924; Berglund, Hilding, 1929; Birrell, Russell G., 1925; Blake, Florence G., 1939; Bourn, Lucy Elizabeth, undated; Bovell, C. H., 1925; Branch, J. R. B., 1929; Bray, Lynda, 1926; Brinkley, Florence, 1925; Brown, Irma Edmiston, 1926; Carney, Mrs. Cyrill (see Last, Ruth M.); Carson, Ruth, 1925; Caulfield, Kathleen, 1924; Chaney, Mary E., 1926; Chen, F. K., 1927; Chen, (Tsu-chen) Katherine, 1924-1929; Chinn, Alexander B., 1929; Chiu, Ding-ying, 1926; Chiu, Mrs. Lloyd, 1923; Chu, Fu-tang, 1929; Chu, Hung-pih, 1929; Colver, Armeda M., 1928; Connell, John William, undated; Connelly, Susan H., 1923; Corbett, Charles H., 1925; Cormack, Robert, 1927; Craig, Mabel, 1925; Crowe, Harold, 1926; Dalrymple, Lila M., 1926, 1938; Daly, Florence E., undated; Dilworth, Jessie G., 1927; Downes, Helen, 1925; Filandino, Elvira, 1927; Firor, Marion P., 1927; Fitzmaurice, Lawrence W., 1926; Fox, Leda Ruth, 1927; Gault, Arabella S., 1925-1926; Goodman, Florence, 1923; Griswold, Laura K., 1927; Gross, Dorothy, 1923; Guy, Ruth H., 1929; Halsey, Marion S., 1924; Hammett, (Miss), 1926; Hardy, Albert W., 1924-1926; Harper, Esther, 1923; Harrell, Virginia, 1925-1926; Harrop, George A., 1924; Holland, Gladys Lemon, 1928; Holland, Helen, 1925; Holiday, (Mr.), 1927; Hosmer, Gertrude, 1926; Hudson, David, 1925-1926; Hull, Dorothy Delyra, 1936; Ingram, Isabel, 1927; Jacobus, Dorothy, 1923; Johnston, Kenneth Vurns, undated; Judd (Miss), 1927; Kelm, H., 1927; Kellers, Irmarita, undated; King, Lucille G., 1929; Knox, Lawrence M., 1924-1926; Kumm, Henry W., 1925-1926; Larson, Mary, 1925-1926; Last, Ruth M. (Mrs. Cyril Carney), 1937; Liu, Shih-hao, 1925; Loh, Anna, 1926; Luther, Jean, 1926; Lynch, Helen, 1926; Ma, Kiam (Ma Chi-ming), undated; MacAlpine, Edith, 1923; McCullough, E. Grace, undated; McCoy, Mary Van S., 1924; McGill, Charles Sherlock, 1924-1925; McIvor, Helen, 1925-1926; MacKensie, Isabel, 1925-1926; McKillop, Marjorie L., 1929; Macmillan, E. B. A. (Mrs.), 1919; Maguire, Clarence, 1927; March, Helen, 1929; Markillie, Mildred, 1936; Meng, Chi-mao, 1925-1926, 1929; Miller, George Gavin, undated; Mills, R. G., undated; Mitchell, Esther, undated; Moo, Priscilla, 1923; Mooney, Mabel, 1925-1926; Mooney, Winifred, 1924; Noser, Elizabeth, 1939; Moy-orne, Pearl, undated; Mu, Jui-wu, 1925; Murray, Emily Tilly (Mrs.), 1925
- Confidential Reports on Staff (N-Y) (Box 34, Folder 238)
  Norelius, Jessie P., 1929; Pai, Hsium-lan, 1923; Peirs, Adeline, 1926; Purcell, Mary, 1925; Ramey, William O., 1926; Rayner, Lavinia K., 1929; Richardson, Esther Pauline, 1924; Rinell, Edith, 1925; Rinell, Margaret, 1925; Robertson, Jean, 1925; Robinson, Ethel E., 1925-1926; Ross, Kathryn D., 1927; Rothe, Resi (Mrs.), 1929; Schmertz, Louis, 1925; Schmidt, Carl, undated; Scott, Annie M., 1929; Scott, Ewing C., 1925; Scott, Mary B., 1929; Severinghaus, Aura (Mr.), 1924-1925; Severinghaus, Leslie (Mr.), 1925-1927; Shen, James K., 1929; Sloan, Leigh E., undated; Smetana, H., 1927; Smyly, H. J., 1929; Stainsby, Wendell-Johnson, 1925-1927; Steffens, Gertrude, undated; Stephenson, Bird R., undated; Sternberg, Alix, 1929; Streichan, Lilah, 1923; Svenson, Ruth, 1925; Swede, Allen, undated; See, Elizabeth, 1924; Tai, Zing-ling, 1925-1926; Tang, Ning-kang, 1925; Taylor, Harry B., 1929; Tennent, Cornelia, 1936; Tilly, Edith, 1925; Tomscik, J., 1927; Tseng, Lily, 1925; Tung, Chen-lang, 1924-1925; Vance, Lucy, 1925-1926; Van Gorder, George W., 1929; Van Sant, Helen, 1926; Whiteside, Faye, 1925-1926; Wight, G. Earle, 1925-1926; Willner, Otto, 1929; Wilson, Stanley D., 1925; Wolf, Edna, 1925; Wooster, Maude, 1924; Wright, Harriet, 1923; Yen, Hui-ching 1924-1926
- Connecticut Medical Examining Board, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 238A)
- Construction, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 239)
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of construction of PUMC, attached to a letter from Greene to Vincent (May 27, 1927).
- Construction, 1928-1933 (Box 34, Folder 240)
- Construction, 1934-1950 (Box 34, Folder 241)
  Anderson, Meyer & Co., Ltd.; Anner; Buildings; Buildings - Anner; Buildings - Director; Buildings - Greene; Buildings - King; Buildings - Woods; Comptroller; Costs - Director; Costs - Greene; Costs - Jewett; Costs - Resident Director; Director; Gee; Greene; Houghton; Mao; Myers; Plans; Plans - Comptroller; Plans - Greene; Plans - Stone & Webster, Inc.; Resident Director; Sewage Ejector - Anner; Sewage Ejector - Stone & Webster, Inc.; Starkweather & Broadhurst, Inc.; Stone & Webster, Inc.; Williams.
- Construction - Power Plant, 1927-1928 (Box 34, Folder 242)
  Anner; Cochrane Corp.; Comptroller; Dashiell; Director; Gee; Greene; Jewett; Logs; Resident Director; Ruggles-Klingemann Manufacturing Co.; Stone & Webster, Inc.; Worthington Pump & Machinery Co.
  See also Oversized Folder 69, Item 7
- Construction - Refrigeration, 1927-1929 (Box 35, Folder 243)
  Anner; Comptroller; Director; Jewett; Greene; Nickerson & Collins Co.; Stone & Webster, Inc.; Vilter Manufacturing Co.; Williams, A. B.; Wilson, S. D.; Yay, Yu-van
- Construction - Water Supply System, 1927, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 244)
  Anner; Comptroller; Director; Greene; Morris Machine Works; Resident Director; Starkweather & Broadhurst; Stone & Webster, Inc.
- Construction - Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 244A)
  Kuam, C. F., 1918; Lewis, Mrs. Charles, 1918; Morse, William R., 1916.
  Items of special note in this folder include a denunciation of work on Sunday, found under the mark-up Construction - Miscellaneous - Lewis; and a corruption accusation (February 30, 1918), found under the mark-up Construction - Miscellaneous - Kuam.
- Cont (Box 35, Folder 245)
  Contingent Fund, 1921-1924 (Goodrich; Greene; Hogg; Houghton; Stoughton); Contracts, 1921-1923 (Houghton)
- Contracts, Settlements of, 1941-1951 (Box 35, Folder 246)
  Balfour; Bowen; Chen, C. C.; Ching, Cheng; Comptroller; Director; Ferguson; Forkner; Li; Loucks; Parker; Sze; Wong, Wen-hao; Wu, Hsien; Yuan, I. C.
  See also Box 161, Folder 1169 (Contracts - Settlement Checks, nos. 1-1986, 1946).
- Conv-Corr (Box 35, Folder 247)
  Convalescent Hostel, 1923-1926; Coolidge, Charles, 1916-1917; Corbett, Charles H., 1963; Corkey, Elizabeth Conrad, 1948; Cornell Medical Quarterly, 1943; Cornell University - Opie, Eugene L., 1931-1942, 1960, 1971
- Cos-Cre (Box 35, Folder 248)
  Cosman, Tanis N., 1952; Council on Health Education, 1924; Councilman, Elizabeth, 1923-1924; Courter, Norman, 1922; Craig, Mabel, 1921-1925, 1931; Crane, Charles R., 1927-1928; Crematorium, 1924-1926
- Criticism, 1914-1932 (Box 35, Folder 249)
  Items of special note in this folder include a report by Peabody on the schools and hospitals visited, includes remarks on UMC (1914).
- Criticism, 1933-1944 (Box 35, Folder 250)
  Amoss; Chen, Chih-chien; Conover, C. T.; Director; Edsall, David; Fitzgerald, A.; Flexner; Formulary; Forkner; Fosdick, R. B.; Gee; Goodrich; Graduate Society of Peking Union Medical Center (PUMC) - Rockefeller, J. D. 3rd; Graduate Society of Peking Union Medical Center (PUMC) - Vincent, G. E.; Greene; Gregg; Gunn; Hastings, A. Baird; Heiser; Hoffmann, William; Houghton; Hsu; Hume; Kavanagh; Lennox, William G.; Lim, C. E.; Liu, James; Manget, F. P.; Maxwell, J. L.; McClure; McKhann; Ministry of Education - Cohn; Ministry of Education - Greene; Ministry of Education - Gunn; Ministry of Education - Richardson, W. S.; Mukerji; Opie, E. L.; Peabody, F. W;. Pearce; Pillat; Resident Director; Robinson, G. Canby; Rockefeller, J.D. Jr.; Snapper; Stampar, A.; Stelle, William B.; Sze; Teusler; Wood, J.; Wright
- Cro-Cur (Box 36, Folder 251)
  Crockford, A. J., 1930-1934; Cruickshank, E. W. H ., 1965; Curran, Jean A., 1955-1956
- Curriculum, 1922-1924 (Box 36, Folder 252)
- Curriculum, 1925-1937 (Box 36, Folder 253)
  Berglund; Black; Dieuaide, F. R.; Director; Downing, A. S.; Dunlap; Faust; Flexner; Gates; Grant, J. B.; Greene; Heisler; Hodges; Houghton; Howard; Lim, C. E.; Ma, Kiam; McLean; MacMillan, E. B. A.; Medical Officers Training Corp.; Medical Officers Training Corp. - Greene; Meleney, H. E.; Peabody; Peterson; Read; Ten Broeck; University of the State of New York - Downing; Vincent; Wilbur; Woods
- Curriculum - Minutes, 1932-1942 (Box 36, Folder 254)
- Curriculum - Nurses, 1924-1937, 1943-1944 (Box 36, Folder 255)
  Downing, A. S.; Greene; Hodgman, G.; Houghton; Ingram, Ruth; McCabe, Anne; Nieh; Resident Director; Stewart, Isabel
- Cutler, Max, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 255A)
- Dai-Deb (Box 36, Folder 256)
  Dai, Bingham, 1935; Das Chagas, Mrs. Mario R., 1960-1966; Deanship, 1919-1920, 1924-1928, 1937-1940, 1948-1950 (Chang, H. C.; Director; Dunlap; Edsall; Greene; Hu, C. H.; Lim, C. E.; Resident Director); Debevoise, Thomas M., 1925-1934
- Dedication, 1917-1923 (Box 36, Folder 257)
  Correspondence (Burton, Ernest D.; Chien; Dickinson, Robert L.; Drew, Edward B.; Eggleston; Embree; Grant, W. Henry; Greene, R. S.; Houghton; Hunan-Yale/Yale Missionary Society; Kirk; MacMillan, E. B. A.; Manson, Patrick; Miller [Miss]; Pearce, R. M.; Presbyterian Mission Hospital - Japan; Presbyterian Mission Hospital - Korea; Rockefeller, J. D. Jr.; Simpson, P. P.; United Free Church of Scotland/Moukden Hospital; Vincent, G. E.; Voorhees); Guest List; Invitation; "Empress of Asia" - Listing/Bulletin; Commemorative Medal; "General Bulletin"; Dedication Programme; Organ Recital Programme; Medical Conference Programme
- Dedication - Addresses, Abstracts of, 1921 (Box 36, Folder 258)
- Dedication - Newspaper Clippings, 1917-1921 (Box 37, Folder 259)
  See also Oversized Folder 69, Item 8.
- Dedication Volume (Manuscript) - Addresses (Box 37, Folder 260)
- Dedication Volume (Manuscript) - Clinic Section (Box 37, Folder 261)
  Medicine; Neurology; Obstetrics & Gynecology; Opthalmology; Otorhinolaringology; Pathology; Surgery
- Dedication Volume (Manuscript) (Box 37, Folder 262)
  Conferences on Leprosy; Conferences on Sprue; Miscellany
- Dedication Volume (Manuscript) - Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 263)
- Dedication Volume (Manuscript) - Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 264)
- Dedication Volume, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 265)
  Cowdry; Goodrich; Houghton; Williamson
- Dedication Volume, 1921 (Box 38, Folder 266)
- Dedication Volume, 1921-1927 (Box 38, Folder 267)
- Dedication Volume - Correspondence / Historical Sketch and Description (Box 38, Folder 268)
- Dentistry, 1920-1940 (Box 38, Folder 269)
  Branch, J. R. B.; Directo;r Eastman Dental Clinic - Anderson; Eastman Dental Clinic - Greene; Greene; Houghton; Mao; Zinninger, Max.
  Items of special note in this folder include a critique by Mack on Division of Oral Surgery, PUMC (1929).
- Dentistry - Staff - Anderson, Bert G., 1922-1935, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 270)
- Dentistry - Staff (B) (Box 39, Folder 271)
  Baranoff, Alexander F., 1925-1936, 1955-1956, 1963-1964; Boots, John L., 1926, 1936, 1939-1949, 1959, 1964-1968
- Dentistry - Staff (Ch-Ma) (Box 39, Folder 272)
  Chang, Fu-chen, 1927; Chang, Hung-chun, 1927; Chen, Hwar, 1931; Claytor, S. O., 1940; Holliday, Houghton, 1925-1930; Koh, John C. K., 1929-1930; Lung, Chih-shan, 1935; Mack, Cornelius H., 1929-1933, 1945; Mahoff, Natalie, 1934; Mao, Hsieh-chuin, 1931-1936, 1939, 1948
- Dentistry - Staff (Mo-Wa) (Box 39, Folder 273)
  Montelius, George A., 1929-1935, 1946; Prentice, Wentworth B., 1928; Wang, Chieh-chuan, 1931-1932, 1940
- Dentistry - Staff (Wo-Yu) (Box 39, Folder 274)
  Wolfe, John J., 1932-1940, 1946-1947, 1957-1958, 1962; Wong, Jee-lum, 1922-1925; Yu, C. C., 1940
- Departments, Work of, 1919-1921 (Box 39, Folder 275)
- Departments, Work of, 1919-1921 (Box 39, Folder 276)
- Dermatology (Box 40, Folder 277)
  General, 1921-1926 (Director; Houghton); Staff (Chen, Foong-kong, 1922-1931; Chin, Tso-liang, 1935)
- Dermatology - Staff - Frazier, C. N., 1919-1937 (Box 40, Folder 278)
- Dermatology - Staff - Frazier, C. N., 1938-1941 (Box 40, Folder 279)
- Dermatology - Staff - Frazier, C. N., 1942-1973 (Box 40, Folder 280)
- Dermatology - Staff (Hall-Li) (Box 40, Folder 281)
  Hall, Giles A. M., 1925-1930; Hu, Chuan-kuei, 1932-1940, 1945-1946; Keim, Harther L., 1926-1927; Li, Hung-chiung, 1933-1939, 1942, 1950
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of Hung-chiung Li.
- Dermatology - Staff (Liu-Wang) (Box 40, Folder 282)
  Liu, Chi-cheng, 1918-1929; Ma, Shou-kou, 1949; Mu, Jui-wu, 1923-1939; Pearce, Louise, 1931-1932, 1959; Tsao, Sung-nien, 1935-1939, 1945; Wang, Kuang-chao, 1941
- Des-Dic (Box 40, Folder 283)
  Deshler, David W., 1918, 1922, 1933; De Schweinitz (see Schweinitz); Dichne, D., 1951; Dick, George F., 1924.
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of an ovarian cyst (July 23, 1951), found under the mark-up Dichne.
- Dietary, 1918-1939 (Box 40, Folder 284)
  Bryan, Mary de Garmo; Comptroller; Director; Goodrich; Greene; Gregg; Houghton; Lusk; Pearce
- Dietary - Staff (Bu-Fa) (Box 41, Folder 285)
  Burkett, Helen (Mrs. Drummond), 1934-1938, 1946; Chang, Mei-li, 1929; Chen, Sabine Shih, 1928; Chen, Shih-kuei, 1926; Chen, Sopie, 1933-1934, 1945; Chen, Yung, 1927; Cheo, Yuan-mei, 1936; Chow, Hsuan, 1937, 1948-1950; Curran, Emily (Mrs. Liang), 1933-1934; Fan, Hsun, 1940.
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of Helen Burkett.
- Dietary - Staff - Fong, Wen-yuen (Frances/Lily), 1930-1937, 1940-1949 (Box 41, Folder 286)
- Dietary - Staff (Go-Lian) (Box 41, Folder 287)
  Gormican, Genevieve, 1932-1936, 1944; Hammett, Betty, 1933-1937; Han, Julia, 1927-1928; Hou, Kuan-hua, 1939, 1950; Hsieh, Helen (Mrs.), 1924-1925; Hsu, Yen-teh, 1930; Huang, Kwe-pau, 1920-1931, 1954; Huang, Li-chen, 1924-1927; Kwan, Kuei-wu, 1941; Kwong, (Shu-chen) Louise, 1926-1927; Lee, Anna (Li, Wan-chieh), 1927-1931; Li, Hsien-chen (Blanche), 1924-1927; Liang, Emily (see Curran)
- Dietary - Staff (Liao-Ne) (Box 41, Folder 288)
  Liao, Su-chin, 1931-1933, 1946; Lin, Ying, 1939; Liu, Tau Miao Keng (Mrs.), 1930; Lu, Chia-yu, 1940; Lusk, Graham, 1919; Lynch, Helen, 1923-1927, 1971; McCullough, Grace, 1917-1925, 1930, 1934; Mitchell, Katherine (see Thoma); Nesbitt, Estelle, 1933-1938, 1945-1952
- Dietary - Staff (P-T) (Box 41, Folder 289)
  Pai, Ho-I, 1936; Richardson, E. Pauline, 1920-1926; Shafer, Alberta, 1925-1932; Sheh, (Li-woo) Lucy, 1940-1941; Suin, Yu-han, 1938, 1947; Tao, Yu-yun, 1925-1926; Thoma, Katherine M. (Mrs.), 1932-1936; Tsiang, Lily Lee (Mrs.) (Li, Fu-hing), 1937-1939, 1958
- Dietary - Staff (W-Y) (Box 41, Folder 290)
  Wang, Te-chin, 1939; Wen, Dorothy, 1933; Wong, (Yuk-lin) Marjorie, 1933-1936, 1957; Wren, U. Y., 1925; Yang, Min-hsien, 1938; Yu, Hsi-hsuan, 1935-1941, 1944
- Die-Dip (Box 41, Folder 291)
  Dietrich, Frederick H., 1918-1922, 1927; Dih, Dorothy, 1946-1947; Diplomas, 1916-1918, 1924-1937 (Debevoise; Director; Downing, Augustus S.; Finley, John H.; Flexner, S.; Greene; Horner, H. H.; Houghton; Lim; Murphy, S. J.; Sullivan, James)
  See also Box 162, Folder 10; Oversized Folder 69, Item 9
- Director - China Medical Board, 1922-1923 (Box 41, Folder 292)
  Greene
  See also Resident Director - China Medical Board
- Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC)
  Greene; Houghton; McLean
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 1916-1918 (Box 42, Folder 293)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 1919 (Box 42, Folder 294)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), January-March 1920 (Box 42, Folder 295)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), April 1920-1921 (Box 42, Folder 296)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), January-August 1922 (Box 42, Folder 297)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), September 1922-May 1924 (Box 42, Folder 298)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), July 1924 (Box 42, Folder 299)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), August 1924 (Box 43, Folder 300)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), September 1924 (Box 43, Folder 301)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), October 1924 (Box 43, Folder 302)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), November 1924 (Box 43, Folder 303)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), December 1924-January 1925 (Box 43, Folder 304)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 1927 (Box 43, Folder 305)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), January-May 1928 (Box 43, Folder 306)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), June-August 1928 (Box 44, Folder 307)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), September-December 1928 (Box 44, Folder 308)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), January-March 1929 (Box 44, Folder 309)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), April-June 1929 (Box 44, Folder 310)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), July-October 1929 (Box 44, Folder 311)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), November-December 1929 (Box 44, Folder 312)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), January-May 1930 (Box 44, Folder 313)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), May-June 1930 (Box 45, Folder 314)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), July-December 1930 (Box 45, Folder 315)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), January-June 1931 (Box 45, Folder 316)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), July-December 1931 (Box 45, Folder 317)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), January-March 1932 (Box 45, Folder 318)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), April-December 1932 (Box 45, Folder 319)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), January-May 1933 (Box 45, Folder 320)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), June-December 1933 (Box 46, Folder 321)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), January-May 1934 (Box 46, Folder 322)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), June-December 1934 (Box 46, Folder 323)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), January-July 1935 (Box 46, Folder 324)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), August-December 1935 (Box 46, Folder 325)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 1936-1937 (Box 46, Folder 326)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 1938 (Box 46, Folder 327)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 1939-1940 (Box 47, Folder 328)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 1941 (Box 47, Folder 329)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 1942-1946 (Box 47, Folder 330)